and so.
無望情緣。
We don't know.
它都 perfunctory。
如果呢個法案被否決，
Will anyone be held responsible?
第一及二以及附表，是否有委員想發言？
We couldn't help to ask still，what does happen？
The fact of the matter is, it's already been spent. The money is already gone.
所以，就係 sort， just a matter of letting it through the procedure.
seeking more than 30 billion extra dollars in government spending.
Because this is the legal setup as such. This is the structural setup in this council.
and judging by the official's reply earlier, nothing much is going to happen. And what are you going to do about it? That's the idea.
This is a perfunctory bill and we're doing a perfunctory debate, as usual, because whatever you say, whatever your suggestions, however smart they are, the government will just choose to ignore.
because we knew even if it got voted down, if it does ever, because with all the Beijing flunkies around, there's no chance that it would be vetoed by the majority as such.
追加撥款二零一八二零一九年度條例草案，本會現在成為全體委員會審議追加撥款二零一八至二零一九年度條例草案。現在嘅待議議題係以下條文納入以下條文及附表納入本條例草案。
用過。
the spending.
propaganda。
Now, if
matter， and。
and this is exactly the case.
We would like to know what exactly happened.
As this bill is so aptly named, supplementary.
We have the right to know. The people have the right to know, but
command a lot of respect from local reporters, but these days,
Some department would need to spend extra on the celebr celebration dues on the whatever issues. Okay, it's for the pleasure, for the entertainment of the local people.
It's not going to happen that members of this council will not agree with the spending, because the money has already gone down. And I wouldn't say gone down the drain, because there are some meaningful or at least understandable.
extra spendings like extra works that were required to clear out after the typhoon hit in Hong Kong, or for that matter, extra welfare spending. Who would object to that? Except
appropriation bill。 The word appropriation is just rather fun because to appropriate could also mean to steal, to take something for for your own use and typically without the owner's consent or permission.
nou
我我。
promoting.
我係説。
We were seeing.
或的 inclusion， of course， we object。
因為這just doesn't sound right。
promotion，但係，what？
and we have every right to say no to them.
all this new propaganda spending on the part of the government is unacceptable.
Hong Kong to the rest of the world for essentially for overseas.
The GIS spending was set to was set needed on the.
this particular department is simply doing government propaganda work, helping the the government to turn Hong Kong into some Orwellian society.
Of course, we are now talking about the consideration of including clauses one and two and shadow stand parts of the bill.
What are they all about? Because we only read in the news not too long ago, a few days ago I think that the big labels in the advertising industry in the world—it's a global thing.
You guys, you you have already passed the spending. We're just doing this for the sake of legislative record, and that's that. You cannot moan about it. But what hit me as unusual is all the extra.
But still, we would like to have a breakdown on exactly what's been spent and what has been done. But the most ironic extra spending, probably, is performed by the GIS, the Government Information Services, which
我啊，我唔方便，聽你翻返嚟呢個辯論好嘛？Yes, I will be, because I for what judging by the vote you've got in the second reading, you knew we're against this entire bill and.
反對嘅證據手。
係，誒張麗雲議。
反對嘅請舉手。
有冇其他議員想發言？
財經事務及服務局局長。
喺程序上面咧，都能夠確保我哋係用得其所嘅。
張麗雲議員要求記名點票，點票鐘響五分鐘。
請各位將手機轉做靜音。
現在嘅代決議題係秘書已讀出嘅條文同埋附表納入本條例草案，贊成嘅請舉手。
現在嘅代議議題係局長嘅議案予以通過。現在提出上述嘅代決議題，贊成嘅請舉手。
We need to ask again. It's public money, and once again, it could be seen as appropriation. Thank you.
Try to urge the local population to endorse the new national security law that's going to be slapped on Hong Kong. How much?
我認為議題係獲得在席委員以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。全體委員會已完成審議，追加撥款。
And if you have noticed in the media, the latest would be about how this Kerri Lamb government is spending on billboards and video duels to.
主席，我簡單回應下。咁第一咧就係今日所追加嗰啲開支咧，其實都係經過財委會啦，同埋相或者係相關嘅一啲嘅授權批准嘅。嚇咁同埋頭先我都解釋過，其實喺我哋每個季度都根據法例有要求咧，係畀嗰個報告咧畀立法會同埋財委會。咁第二咧就係其實每年我哋收完啲錢，都有獨立審計嘅。咁呢？
二零一八、二零一九年度條例草案嘅所有程序，現在回覆為立法會財經事務及庫務局局長。誒，主席，我現在向立法會作出報告，追加撥款二零一八至二零一九年度條例草案，冇經修正而獲全體委員會通過，我動議本會採納此報告嘅議案。現
開始表決。
請核對所在表決。
如果冇問題，要係停止表決，顯示結果。
三讀追加撥款，二零一八至二零一九年度。
出席五十五位，有三位贊成，十九位反對。議題係獲得在席議員以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。